ballerstatus.com 2008-12-16

# BallerStatus.com | Privacy Policy

|  |  |   
---  
  
We respect the privacy of our newsletter subscribers, customers, contacts, those who answer our surveys, and those who fill out our questionnaires. It is our policy: Choice and Consent: To respect the purpose for which our site visitors gave us information. We give users choice and consent over how their personal information is used, and remove names immediately upon request.

**Third Party Use**

To not sell, rent, or loan our subscriber or customer lists to third parties for e-mail marketing. While we sell advertising in our e-mail publications to other companies, we never allow third parties any other use of these subscriber lists.

**Unsubscriptions**

To send our periodicals only to those who request them (that is, opt-in). We immediately unsubscribe those who request it through convenient unsubscribe links in every e-mailing. Our welcome message to subscribers and every issue of our newsletters/e-zine's clearly explain how to unsubscribe. We keep our subscription lists as clean as possible to prevent obsolete e-mail addresses which use unnecessary bandwidth.

**Cookies**

To use cookies in a responsible manner to help our visitors, not snoop on them. We use cookies to: (a) to help rotate banner advertising; (b) to identify shoppers with their shopping carts; (c) to make it easy to order a second time; (d) to allow subscribers to store passwords in cookies if they desire; and (e) to give proper credit for sales made through links on our affiliates' sites. We do not collect or use information from cookies to develop a profile about our visitors or shoppers.

**Security**

To store subscriber and password files with personal information in a secure manner. We store such files in areas not accessible to Web browsers, behind password protection, or off-line.

**Termination**

To continue this policy beyond the termination of our company. If a majority portion of the assets of our company were to be acquired by another organization, that might include our subscriber and other lists, but only as part of a clear agreement binding that organization to abide by the spirit and letter of our privacy policy.

If you have any concerns or questions about our privacy policy or information collected on our sites, please contact us at info@ballerstatus.com  
  
  |  |   
---  
|  |  |  |  |   
---  
|   |  News  
Tourist Shops Making A Killing From Obama Merch  
It's no secret President-elect Barack Obama is more than a politician, he's one of the biggest celebrities in the country. ... full story  
---|---  
 |  Features  
J.J. Fad: Remember Us?  
J.J. Fad, an acronym for Just Jamming Fresh and Def, is comprised of MC J.B. (Juana Burns), Baby-D (Dania Birks) and ... full story  
 |  Editorials & Columns  
Soulstice From France Blog #2: Days 1-3  
As Amanda pointed out, although the Baltimore airport is called Baltimore Washington International, we've never been ... full story  
 |  Beyond Hip-Hop  
Shopping Guide: Holidays Edition 2008  
It's the 2008 holiday season, and with a week and a half of shopping left until Christmas Day, the staff over here at ... full story  
 |  Video  
Brian McKnight Talks Xmas Album On The 'Today Show'  
Brian McKnight appears on the "Today Show" to talk about his latest Christmas album, I'll Be Home For Christmas, previews ... full story
